// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Were you …. This picture at 8 clock yesterday?",
    answer: "sending",
    options: ["Sent", "Are sending", "send", "sending"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Yesterday, The rain  …. Harder and harder.",
    answer: "was getting",
    options: ["Are getting", "getting", "will get", "was getting"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "My friend …. Book to Faradilla at seven clock last night.",
    answer: "was giving",
    options: ["Gave", "Gives", "is giving", "was giving"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Tamara and Tania … to Surabaya at this time last week?",
    answer: "were going",
    options: ["Go", "Going", "was going", "were going"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Yesterday, my mother … a rice when I ate Donut.",
    answer: "was cooking",
    options: ["Is cooking", "Will cooking", "cooked", "was cooking"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "... was watching tv when she called",
    answer: "i",
    options: ["we", "they", "i", "me and my friend"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "I ... paying attention while i was writing the letter, so i made several mistakes",
    answer: "wasn't",
    options: ["weren't", "wasn't", "isn't", "hadn't"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "i didn't like them because they ... always complaining",
    answer: "were",
    options: ["were", "was", "had", "has"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "he was constanly ... He annoyed everyone",
    answer: "talking",
    options: ["talked", "talking", "will talk", "was talked"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "... were eating dinner, discussing their plans and having a good time",
    answer: "they",
    options: ["he", "she", "they", "it"],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
